{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680211396","data":{"timestamp":" 947680211395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 0e42e32b-2591-4123-ad44-31b1f59a2747"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KA"," userResponse":" KA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680212426","data":{"timestamp":" 947680212426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 0e42e32b-2591-4123-ad44-31b1f59a2747"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KA"," userResponse":" KA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680217250","data":{"timestamp":" 947680217250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 0e42e32b-2591-4123-ad44-31b1f59a2747"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KE"," userResponse":" KE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680218297","data":{"timestamp":" 947680218297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 0e42e32b-2591-4123-ad44-31b1f59a2747"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KE"," userResponse":" KE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680224378","data":{"timestamp":" 947680224378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 0e42e32b-2591-4123-ad44-31b1f59a2747"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680224485","data":{"timestamp":" 947680224485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 0e42e32b-2591-4123-ad44-31b1f59a2747"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KE"," userResponse":" KE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680234871","data":{"timestamp":" 947680234871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680235093","data":{"timestamp":" 947680235093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680236055","data":{"timestamp":" 947680236055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680237327","data":{"timestamp":" 947680237327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680240235","data":{"timestamp":" 947680240235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680241078","data":{"timestamp":" 947680241078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680241391","data":{"timestamp":" 947680241390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680242623","data":{"timestamp":" 947680242623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680246157","data":{"timestamp":" 947680246157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680247140","data":{"timestamp":" 947680247140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680247393","data":{"timestamp":" 947680247393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680248336","data":{"timestamp":" 947680248336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680251168","data":{"timestamp":" 947680251167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680252201","data":{"timestamp":" 947680252201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680252674","data":{"timestamp":" 947680252673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680257183","data":{"timestamp":" 947680257182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680257250","data":{"timestamp":" 947680257250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 341e5d94-36fa-47d9-827e-e9cf34073ca3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680271054","data":{"timestamp":" 947680271054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680275310","data":{"timestamp":" 947680275310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680287584","data":{"timestamp":" 947680287584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680293433","data":{"timestamp":" 947680293433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680298123","data":{"timestamp":" 947680298123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680302456","data":{"timestamp":" 947680302455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680307812","data":{"timestamp":" 947680307812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680312069","data":{"timestamp":" 947680312069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680327799","data":{"timestamp":" 947680327799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680332444","data":{"timestamp":" 947680332444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680338201","data":{"timestamp":" 947680338200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" 5a843af1-8e15-46ce-a9c0-941897a8f4bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680356418","data":{"timestamp":" 947680356418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680362259","data":{"timestamp":" 947680362259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680368777","data":{"timestamp":" 947680368777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680375740","data":{"timestamp":" 947680375740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680387054","data":{"timestamp":" 947680387054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-2-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680405996","data":{"timestamp":" 947680405996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680417201","data":{"timestamp":" 947680417200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_11-1-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680435144","data":{"timestamp":" 947680435144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-5-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680452068","data":{"timestamp":" 947680452068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680461403","data":{"timestamp":" 947680461403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680468008","data":{"timestamp":" 947680468008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680474237","data":{"timestamp":" 947680474237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680480854","data":{"timestamp":" 947680480853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_151046"," gameId":" e7f70cd5-3f8a-48f7-9153-75c9c309bc33"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF10-BL1.incr.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}